ssir.org 2018-12-25

# Privacy Policy

At _Stanford Social Innovation Review_ , we want you to enjoy and benefit from our websites and online services secure in the knowledge that we have implemented fair information practices designed to protect your privacy. Our privacy policy below describes the information we collect, how we use it, and the choices you have regarding collection and use of your personal information.

Please read this privacy policy carefully. **Your use of and/or registration on any aspect of the website will constitute your agreement to this privacy policy.** If you cannot agree with the terms and conditions of this privacy policy, please do not use the website. This privacy policy does not cover information collected elsewhere, including without limitation offline and on sites linked to from the website.

In addition to reviewing this privacy policy, please read our [Terms of Use](https://www.stanford.edu/site/terms/). Your use of the website constitutes agreement to its terms and conditions as well.

This privacy policy may be modified from time to time; the date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page, so check back often. Continued access of the website by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the privacy policy.

### What Information the Website Collects

Our site may automatically recognize your domain name, IP address, browser version, operating system, and the website you passed through to reach us. In addition, our site automatically gathers certain usage information, like the numbers and frequency of visits to the site and its areas—very much like television ratings that tell how many people tuned in to a program.

Some features of our site offer you the option of providing information such as your name, email address, postal address, phone number, organization, location, or any other identifying information. As described in greater detail below, such information will only be used to provide you with products or services you have requested, or additional information about the sites or its affiliates. (You may also provide us with such information in the course of subscribing to _Stanford Social Innovation Review_ magazine or other offerings from _Stanford Social Innovation Review_ —details of how we use such information are also provided below.)

### How the Website Uses Information You Provide

The information the website collects is used to improve the content of _Stanford Social Innovation Review_ magazine and its site, and to keep you apprised of important developments. For example, we may use personally identifiable information to contact you as part of an online survey about our editorial offerings, inform you of material changes or additions to our services, advise you of account status, or contact you in order to comply with any legal requirements. Also, we compile and use your information so that we may keep you apprised of special offers, as well as additional products that may be of interest to you.

In some cases, we may share personally identifiable information to contact you (sometimes through a vendor or business partner) for the reasons we have described.

We will not sell any personally identifying information obtained through the site. We do not collect personally identifying information from our visitors, other than what is supplied to us on a voluntary basis. From time to time we allow reputable companies, whose products or services we feel may interest our enewsletter subscribers, to contact these subscribers using the addresses provided to us during the process of subscribing to _Stanford Social Innovation Review_ ’s print edition.

We may provide statistical usage data in the aggregate—not information about you personally—to our partners about how visitors use the sites. From time to time, we conduct research on our users’ demographics, interests, and behavior based on the information you provide to us upon registration, on order forms, as well as from our server log files or from surveys. We do this to better understand and serve our users. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis, and we may share this aggregated data with advertisers or other businesses.

In some cases, we may disclose information about you to a third party if we are required to do so by law or if we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to comply with the law or legal process, to protect and defend our rights or to prevent misuse of our sites, or to protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public.

In the event of a corporate change in control resulting from, for example, a sale to, or merger with, another entity, or in the event of a sale of assets or a bankruptcy, _Stanford Social Innovation Review_ reserves the right to transfer your personally identifiable information to the new party in control or the party acquiring assets.

### Cookies and Analytics

Cookies are tiny data files that web sites commonly write to your hard drive when you visit them so that they can remember you when you visit. A cookie file contains information that can identify you anonymously and maintain your account's privacy. Our service uses cookies to maintain a user's identity between sessions so that the site can be personalized based on user preferences or a user's history. We may use information collected using third party cookies (for example, Google AdSense and DoubleClick) and Web beacons on our services to deliver _Stanford Social Innovation Review's_ advertising displayed to you on third party sites. We also use cookie information to know when you return to our site after visiting these third party sites. We also use analytics services (such as Google Analytics and others) to help analyze how users use the services. These analytics services use cookies to collect and store information such as how often users visit the Services, what pages they visit, and what other sites they used prior to coming to the services. We also use the information from these analytics services to improve our services and to provide reporting to our partners regarding site activity and utilization. Please see the following links for more information about Google Analytics, DoubleClick, and Google AdSense: http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/ and http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/.

You can set your web browser to prompt you before you accept a cookie, accept cookies automatically or reject all cookies. However, if you choose not to accept cookies from this web site, then you may not be able to access and use all or part of this web site or benefit from the information and services which it offers.

### Web Beacons

Pages on the services and emails that _Stanford Social Innovation Review_ sends to you may contain small image files called web beacons. Web beacons are used as a mechanism to help us track your visits to our site and whether or not you open our emails. In addition, we use several third-party services that embed web beacons on our site for similar tracking purposes. These third-party services are used to provide additional features to users, such as the ability to share content on our site with your social network.

### Links

The services contains links to other third-party sites. _Stanford Social Innovation Review_ is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third-party sites.

### Information Security and Notification

Because no data transmission over the Internet is completely secure, and no system of physical or electronic security is impenetrable, the _Stanford Social Innovation Review_ can not guarantee the security of the information you send to us or the security of our servers or databases, and by using the website you agree to assume all risk in connection with the information sent to us or collected by us when you use the website. In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you. If notification is appropriate, we may notify you by email (provided we have your email address).

### Kids and Parents

This website is not intended for use by children, especially those under age 13. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information or use our public discussion areas, forums, and chats. Minors between the ages of 13 and 17 must get the permission of their parent(s) or legal guardian(s) before making purchases, including subscriptions, on this site.

If your children disclose information about themselves in publicly accessible areas of the website, they may get unsolicited messages from other parties. Accordingly, you should tell them not to do so.

### Unsubscribe and Data Deletion

If you would like to unsubscribe from our communications at any time, please [click here](http://cl.exct.net/unsub_center.aspx?qs=5ac6ca7e00c143cadb2f6066daa2894df23c4f459042895678898e042f10d95021775c156c0aefe75d02de36048ab8e85742b506e85d147ae4b69253c9722f9bc96bff03e757b6df) or you may do so in the footer of any of our emails. If you would like us to delete your information entirely, please contact us at [privacy@ssir.org](mailto:privacy@ssir.org).

### Questions?

If you have any concerns or questions about any aspect of this policy, or to be removed from all email lists, contact us at [privacy@ssir.org](mailto:privacy@ssir.org) or at the postal address below.

Attn: Digital Privacy Officer

Stanford Social Innovation Review  
Stanford University  
PO Box 20441  
Stanford, CA. 94309-0441

5/21/2018
